http://www.microbac.com/privacy

ENVIRONMENTAL ENVIRONMENTAL ComplianceSpecialtyResidential WaterSARS-CoV-2 Environmental Surface TestSARS-CoV-2 Wastewater TestConsultants Engineerswater systemsIndustry ManufacturingOil gas miningfederal governmentwaste managementBrownfieldsFOODFOODSafety & QualityClaims & AuthenticityEnvironmental MonitoringRegulation & ConsultingLIFE SCIENCESLIFE SCIENCESAntimicrobial EfficacyClinical MicrobiologyVirologyLS ChemistryToxicologyDISINFECTANT EFFICACY TESTING FOR THE CORONAVIRUS (SARS-CoV-2)BiopharmaceuticalPharmaceuticalMedical DevicesCosmetics Personal CareABOUTABOUTOverviewHistoryLeadershipCareer oppslocationsCertifications ListAXIS PortalNewsRequest TestingCOVID-19 Launchpad
Toggle navigation
LocationsCareersAXIS™
EnvironmentalENVIRONMENTAL Offering accredited microbiology, chemistry, and molecular capabilities and methods, our environmental teams are responsive to your demands with a focus on quality data and service. We provide routine and specialty analytical testing to assist a broad range of companies and government agencies with their compliance reporting.
Analytical TestingRoutine Analytical & ComplianceSpecialty AnalyticalResidential Well WaterCOVID-19/SARS-CoV-2SARS-CoV-2 Environmental Surface TestSARS-CoV-2 Wastewater TestIndustries ServedConsultants & EngineersUtilities & Water SystemsIndustrial & ManufacturingEnergy, Fuels, & MiningFederal GovernmentWaste ManagementBrownfields & RedevelopmentFoodFOODFrom farm to fork, Microbac helps our clients manage food quality and safety risks to protect consumers and their brands. Our industry expertise and analytical strength support your food safety programs for compliance with FSMA regulations. As an ISO 17025-accredited supplier for end-to-end food testing, we serve all food industry segments with services to meet unique needs.
Testing ServicesSafety & Quality TestingNutritional Analyses & Label ClaimsEnvironmental MonitoringShelf Life & Stability StudiesLife SciencesLIFE SCIENCESOur scientists collaborate with your project teams throughout the product life cycle and bring technical expertise in product safety, quality, efficacy, and stability. We offer an array of studies per industry-specific protocols, including cGMP/GLP/GCP, AOAC, USP and ASTM.
Testing ServicesAntimicrobial EfficacyClinical MicrobiologyVirologyProduct ChemistryToxicologyDISINFECTANT EFFICACY TESTING FOR THE CORONAVIRUS (SARS-CoV-2)Industries ServedBiopharmaceuticalPharmaceuticalMedical DevicesCosmetics & Personal CareAboutABOUTHere at Microbac Laboratories, our team of experts are always looking to serve you and your business with premier expertise and respect for your unique market requirements. Our diverse work portfolio includes broad analytical offerings and tested insights across the environmental, food and life science markets and with 50 years of honing our craft, we offer results you can trust.
About UsAbout UsHistoryLeadershipCareersResourcesLocationsCertificationsAXISNews Contact Us
COVID-19
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICYLast update: February 23, 2017IntroductionMicrobac Laboratories, Inc. ("Microbac" or “Company”) takes your privacy and the security of your personal information very seriously.  Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy and learn about Microbac’s general privacy and information security principles.  This Privacy Policy applies to Microbac’s website, www.microbac.com, (the “Website”), as well as to Microbac’s software-as-a-service platform that is marketed under the name “AXIS™” (the “Platform”).  This Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites operated by Microbac.  Other websites maintained by Microbac may be governed by separate agreements.  In particular, while this Privacy Policy applies to the Platform, the Platform is subject to its own End User Services Agreement (the “EUSA”) and terms herein may be superseded by that agreement.This Privacy Policy applies to the information collected from you while you are using the Website and the Platform, as well as e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and the Website and/or Platform.  As you use the Website and the Platform, we want to be clear about the information we collect about you and how we use that information.  Different parts of the Website and the Platform collect different pieces of information, depending upon which features of the Website and/or Platform you are using and if you are a visitor or a registered user.This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Microbac or any third-party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website and/or Platform.For more information regarding use of the Website, please visit our Website’s Terms of Use. For more information regarding use of the Platform, please access the EUSA provided to registered users and made available via the Platform’s portal. The Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of our Terms of Use and the EUSA.  As part of the Terms of Use and the EUSA, the Privacy Policy constitutes a legally binding agreement between you and Microbac.  By accessing and using our Website, its services and/or the Platform, you agree that you have read, understand and are bound by the terms and conditions set forth herein. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY PART OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR THE TERMS OF USE OR THE EUSA (IF YOU ARE A USER OF THE PLATFORM), PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE WEBSITE, ITS SERVICES OR THE PLATFORM.  This Privacy Policy may change from time to time.  Your continued use of this Website and/or the Platform after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.ChildrenOur Website, services and the Platform are not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children.  If you are under the age of 13, please stop using our Website, services and the Platform.  It is our policy not to knowingly solicit or permit children under the age of 13 to provide their personal information for any purpose.This Privacy Policy explains:• What information we collect• How we use the information• How we share the informationWhat Information We CollectIn general, you can use and visit our Website without submitting any personal information; however, in order to utilize and access other features, you will need to submit your personal information.  We collect information from you when you register on our Website, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or contact us for customer care or technical support.  When using certain features on our Website, you may be required to enter personal information, including, without limitation, your name, e-mail address and phone number.  If you have questions about a Microbac offering that you have purchased, we may also collect information related to that purchase or your use of that purchase.Certain areas of our Website, including Career Opportunities portal, may ask you for additional personal information.  This may include résumés and/or other information about your professional and employment history.  Further, your use of the Platform may require you to share your name, e-mail address, phone number and other information relating to the business or Microbac customer with which you are associated.  For more information on the foregoing, please visit our Terms of Use for the Website or the EUSA for the Platform, or contact us at website.privacy@microbac.com.When you visit or interact with our Website or the Platform, we or our third-party service providers may use cookies and other types of web technologies to collect technical and usage information such as browsing history, domain name, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, data and time of each visit, and pages that your web browser has visited.  Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the website or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information in order to collect technical and usage information such as browsing history, domain name, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, data and time of each visit, and pages that your web browser has visited.We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and to compile aggregate data about Website and Platform traffic and Website and Platform interaction so that we can offer better user experiences and tools to you in the future.Most web browsers permit you to set your web browser to block or delete all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us.  However, it’s important to remember that our services may not function properly if you set your browser to reject cookies. We may use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of the Website and/or Platform. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit our Website, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to our Website.  We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our services.  Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit our Website and/or Platform, rather than your name or other identifying information.  We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information.  Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our Website and/or Platform, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google.  Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our Website and/or Platform is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.  You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to our Website and/or Platform by disabling cookies on your browser.  We may also use other third-party service providers to track our visitors.  We do not combine the information collected through the use of any third-party service providers with personally identifiable information.How We Use InformationAny of the information we collect from you may be used in the following ways:• To personalize and optimize your experience using the Website and the Platform• To understand, monitor and improve the performance of the Website and the Platform• To provide you with technical services if you are or become a customer of Microbac• To respond to your requests and inquiries, or to process any applications submitted to us via the Career Opportunities portal• To process transactions and administer our services, including delivering purchased products or services• To administer a promotion, survey or other Website feature• To send periodic emails, including delivering information (including marketing material) to you that you have requested or that we believe may interest you, such as administrative notices, details of our services, updates on scientific or technical developments and communications relevant to your use of our Website.• To receive and process information relating to your use of the Platform and the services provided by the Platform to you or your employer, or to receive and process requests for additional services requested by you or your employer as they relate to the Platform, subject to the EUSA• For any other purpose where you have provided your consentHow We Share InformationOur policy is to not sell, trade, disclose, share or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, unless you give us your consent or direct us to do so.  We may, however, share your information to third-parties who assist us in operating our Website, the Platform, conducting our business, or servicing you (e.g., marketing).  We may also share your information when we believe the disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law or legal process, enforce our policies, or protect ours or others rights, property or safety.We reserve the right to transfer any personal information we have about you in the event we transfer all or a portion of our business or assets.  Should such a transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information you have provided through this Website and/or the Platform in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.SecurityYou should be aware that information sent to us using this Website, the Platform or e-mail may not be secure in transmission. Please be aware of this when sending any communications.  We cannot (and do not) guarantee absolute security.Changes to our Privacy PolicyOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time.  If we decide to materially change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice of those changes on the Website.Third Party WebsitesOur Website may contain links to other websites such as social networks and links to our business partners.  Please be aware that we do not endorse and are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and the Privacy Policy presented here does not apply to such websites.   If you have any questions about these other companies’ data practices, you should review their privacy policies.Your California Privacy RightsCalifornia Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please send an e-mail to website.privacy@microbac.com or write us at: ATTN: Office of General Counsel, 101 Bellevue Road, Suite 301, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania 15229.Ownership of MaterialsMicrobac owns the information sent to us by means of this Website.  If you choose to send us an e-mail message (including submission of your résumé), we may retain the content of the e-mail, your e-mail address and our response.Contact Information and RegistrationIf there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by sending an email to website.privacy@microbac.com or by sending registered mail to:Microbac Laboratories, Inc.One Allegheny SquareSuite 400Pittsburgh, PA 15212Attn: LegalMicrobac Laboratories, Inc. © 2017. All Rights Reserved.
Locations
Axis™
Careers
Contact
Privacy|Terms & Conditions|Copyright ©2019 Microbac Laboratories, Inc. All rights reserved.|
